Modern Life Is Rubbish is a romance, music film directed by Daniel Jerome Gill.
Brought together by their shared love of music, ten years
on Liam and Natalie are at breaking point.
In their case opposites attract but don't necessarily work long-term.
Making the difficult decision to separate, they must
split their prized music library.
But the soundtrack that defined their relationship
keeps pulling them back together.
Natalie, played by Freya Mavor.
Liam, played by Josh Whitehouse.
Adrian, played by Tom Riley.
Kerry, played by Jessie Cave.
Olly, played by Will Merrick.
Joshua George Whitehouse (born 27 February 1990) is an
English actor, musician and artist.
His films include Northern Soul (2014), Modern Life Is
Rubbish (2017), and Valley Girl (2020).
On television, he is known for his roles in the BBC One series Poldark
(2017–2018) and the Amazon Prime series Daisy Jones & the Six (2023).
The film explores themes of london, england, relationship
problems, relationship, break-up, music fan.
The tone is emotional.